Right, there, I'm finished.
You're finished.
I'm finished.
I'm done.
I mean, I think it's done.
Do you want me to have a read?
No.
No, it's fine. Unless... do you want to?
Do you want me to?
Right, yeah, no, no, you probably should.
Okay?
Actually, can you not?
No.
No, and it's not that I don't want you to.
I do, obviously.
It's just, I know you'll find those wrong with it.
And then you'll make me change it and make you change it.
And then I'll start worrying about all the other things
to wrong with it.
I won't make you change it.
And then I'll never actually send it
and we'll be right back where we started.
Alice, I won't make you change it.
Yes you would, you always make me change things.
Like when?
Last week! Last week I left at work in the kitchen!
I just made some notes in the margin. I was trying to make it sound less dry.
It was a shipping contract. It was supposed to sound dry.
Look, I'd rather just send it, okay?
Good! I want you to just send it!
Fine, I will.
Okay, all right, maybe you should take a look.
actually no seriously I'm sorry I'm sorry okay I just I want to get it right
I'm going to do one more draft.
Done 15.
I need to check the spelling.
Run spell check.
I have. I need to check the stuff it missed.
Like what?
I don't know, that's why I need to check it.
This email is the most important thing I've ever done.
I don't want it to open with dear mum and dad,
I have something really important to tell you.
I'm a Lebanon.
Look, Fee, it's late. They'll be in bed. Can't we just wait?
Wait.
Till when?
I don't know. January?
What, in 24 hours?
Yes, maybe it can wait 24 hours.
Okay.