Right, then. It's finished.
You're finished.
I'm finished, I'm done. I mean, I think it's done.
You want me to have a read?
No, no, it's fine unless you want to
You want me to?
Right. Yeah. No, no, you probably should
Okay?
Actually, can you not?
No.
No, and it's not that I don't want you to.
I do, obviously.
It's just, I know you'll find out what's wrong with it,
and then you'll make me change it and then I'll start worrying about all the other things
that are wrong with it.
I won't make you change it.
And then I'll never actually send it
and we'll be right back where we started.
Alice, I won't make you change it.
Yes, you would. You always make me change things.
Like when?
Last week! Last week I left at work in the kitchen!
I just made some notes in the margin. I was trying to make it sound less dry.
It was a shipping contract. It was supposed to sound dry.
Look, I'd rather just send it, okay?
Good. I want you to just send it.
Time! I will!
Okay, alright. Maybe you should take a look.
Why?
Actually, no.
Seriously?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, okay. I just want to get it right.
I'm going to do one more draft.
You've done 15.
I need to check the spelling.
Run spell check.
I have.
I need to check the stuff it missed.
Like what?
I don't know.
That's why I need to check it
The serial is the most important thing I've ever done.
I don't want it to open with,
Dear Mum and Dad, I have something really important to tell you. I'm a Lebanon.
Look, Phi. It's late. They'll be in bed. Can't we just wait?
To what?
I don't know. January?
What, in 24 hours?
Yes, maybe it can wait 24 hours.
Okay